Inventory of the Richard Throssel Papers, 1900-1993 (bulk 1902-1933)
University of Wyoming. American Heritage Center.
- Photographs and Negatives, 1902-ca. 1920s; Series I.; 14.86 cubic ft. (6 letter boxes, 1 F24 box, 39 negative boxes, 5 shoe boxes and 4 F20 boxes).
  - 8x10 and 5 x 7 Glass Plate Negatives and Photographs, Subseries I.
    - Man - Unidentified (Box 3, Folder 2)
      TP445
      Throssel #681
    - Man - Unidentified (Box 3, Folder 2)
      TP446
      Throssel #682
    - "Lone Elk - Son of Brave Wolf" Cheyenne (Box 3, Folder 2)
      TP447
      Throssel #683
    - "Curly" Crow (Box 3, Folder 2)
      TP448
      Throssel ID #6906 "©"07
      Throssel #684
    - "Lone Elk - Son of Brave Wolf" Cheyenne (Box 3, Folder 2)
      TP448A
      Throssel #696
    - "Fire Bear" Crow (Box 3, Folder 2)
      TP449
      Throssel #685
    - "Curly - Custer's Only Survivor" Crow (Box 3, Folder 2)
      TP450
      AHC Neg. #25151
      Throssel ID #6P012 "©"06
      Throssel #686
    - "Curly" Crow (Box 3, Folder 2)
      TP451
      Throssel #687
    - "White Hawk" Cheyenne (Box 3, Folder 2)
      TP452
      Throssel ID #6941 "©"08
      Throssel #688
    - Crow Man (Box 3, Folder 3)
      TP453
      Throssel #689
    - Crow Man (Box 3, Folder 3)
      TP454
      Throssel #690
    - "Packs the Hat" Crow (Box 3, Folder 3)
      TP455
      Throssel #691
    - "Little Man" Crow (Box 3, Folder 3)
      TP456
      Throssel ID #6853 "©"07
      Throssel #693
    - "Boo Ah Xeesh" (Fish Swims) Crow (Box 3, Folder 3)
      TP457
      Throssel #695
    - Man - Unidentified (Box 3, Folder 3)
      TP458
      Throssel #981
    - "Two Leggings" (Box 3, Folder 3)
      TP459
      Throssel #982
    - "A Cheyenne Woman" (Box 3, Folder 3)
      TP460
    - Baby (Box 3, Folder 3)
      TP461
    - "The Bead Worker" Crow "Clara White (Box 3, Folder 3)
      TP462
      AHC Neg. #25712
      Throssel #700
    - Arrow Maker (Box 3, Folder 4)
      TP463
      AHC Neg. #25725
      Throssel #705
    - "Painting the Sign of his Medicine" (Box 3, Folder 4)
      TP464
      Throssel #706
    - "Painting the Sign of his Medicine" (Box 3, Folder 4)
      TP464A
      Throssel #706A
    - Crow Woman - Outdoors (Box 3, Folder 4)
      TP465
      Negative Box 31
      Throssel #707
    - Crow Man Inside Tipi (Box 3, Folder 4)
      TP466
      Throssel #708
    - Crow Man Inside Tipi (Box 3, Folder 4)
      TP466A
    - Man - Outdoor Portrait (Box 3, Folder 4)
      TP467
      Throssel ID #6839 "©"08
      Throssel #709
    - Girl with Dog (Box 3, Folder 4)
      TP468
      Throssel #710
    - "Plenty Coups" with Horse (Box 3, Folder 4)
      TP469
      Throssel #711
    - Children - Not Crow (Box 3, Folder 4)
      TP470
      Throssel #712
    - "The Scout" - Crow (Box 3, Folder 4)
      TP471
      Throssel #713
    - Crow Boy (Box 3, Folder 4)
      TP472
      Throssel #714
    - Crow Man and Woman Inside Tipi (Box 3, Folder 5)
      TP473
      Throssel #715
    - Crow Woman Seated (Box 3, Folder 5)
      TP474
      Throssel #721
    - "Sitting Bird" Crow "Grandmother of Myrtle Strong Enemy" (Box 3, Folder 5)
      TP475
      Throssel #724
      1 nitrate negative 4 x 6
    - "Sitting Bird" Crow (Box 3, Folder 5)
      TP476
      Throssel #725
    - "Albert And Mary Lincoln" Crow (Box 3, Folder 5)
      TP477
      Throssel #726
    - "Knows the Ground and Wife Eva with Adopted Boy Named Joe" Crow (Box 3, Folder 5)
      TP478 and TP478A
      Throssel #727
    - Cuts the Bear's Ears'" Wife (Box 3, Folder 5)
      TP479
      Throssel #728
    - "Mr. and Mrs. Alfred Blackbird" Crow (Box 3, Folder 5)
      TP480
      Throssel #729
    - "Albert Lincoln" (Box 3, Folder 5)
      TP481
      Throssel #730
    - Crow Woman Braiding Hair (Box 3, Folder 5)
      TP482
      Throssel #733
    - Crow Woman with Beaded Bag in Front of Painted Tipi (Box 3, Folder 6)
      TP483
      Throssel #735
    - Crow Woman (Box 3, Folder 6)
      TP484
      Throssel #736
    - Women and Children (Box 3, Folder 6)
      TP485
      Throssel #737
    - "The Modern Madonna" (Box 3, Folder 6)
      TP486
      Throssel ID #6X038 "©" 1912
      Throssel #734
    - Crow Woman (Box 3, Folder 6)
      TP487
      Throssel #738
    - "In the Laundry" (Box 3, Folder 6)
      TP488
      Negative Box 32
      Throssel #739
    - "Mrs. John Adams (Emma) with Two Girls" Crow (Box 3, Folder 6)
      TP489
      Throssel #740
    - "Sees with His Ears" Crow (Box 3, Folder 6)
      TP490
      Throssel #741
    - Man - Unidentified (Box 3, Folder 6)
      TP491
      Throssel #742
    - Man - Unidentified (Box 3, Folder 6)
      TP492
      Throssel #743
    - "Shot in the Hand" ("Bah Ox Bish, from the Big Horn District") Crow (Box 3, Folder 7)
      TP493
      Throssel #744
    - Two Young Crow Women (Box 3, Folder 7)
      TP494
      Throssel #745
    - Women and Children (Box 3, Folder 7)
      TP495
      Throssel #746
    - "Henry Pretty on Top" Smoking Pipe - Crow (Box 3, Folder 7)
      TP496
      Throssel #747
    - Crow Boy (Box 3, Folder 7)
      TP497
      Throssel #748
    - Crow Boy (Box 3, Folder 7)
      TP498
      Throssel #749
    - Crow Boy (Box 3, Folder 7)
      TP499
      Throssel #750
    - Cabin and Tipi (Box 3, Folder 7)
      TP500
      AHC Neg. #15664
    - Tipi Frame (Box 3, Folder 7)
      TP501
      Throssel #751
    - Tipi Frame (Box 3, Folder 7)
      TP501A
    - Tipi Frame (Box 3, Folder 7)
      TP502
      Throssel #752
    - Tipi Frame (Box 3, Folder 7)
      TP503
      Throssel #752A
    - Tipi Frame (Box 3, Folder 7)
      TP504
      Throssel #752B
    - (Tipi Frame) (Box 3, Folder 7)
      TP505
      Throssel #752C
    - Tipi Frame (Box 3, Folder 8)
      TP506
      Throssel #753
    - Tipi Frame (Box 3, Folder 8)
      TP506A
    - Tipi Frame (Box 3, Folder 8)
      TP507
      Throssel #754
    - "The Deserted Sundance Lodge" (Box 3, Folder 8)
      TP508
      Throssel ID #6987 "©" 07
      Throssel #755
    - Tipi Frame (Box 3, Folder 8)
      TP509
      AHC Neg. #25699
      Throssel #756
    - Four Sweat Lodge Frames (Box 3, Folder 8)
      TP510
      Throssel #757
    - "The Sweat Tipi" with Man Emerging (Box 3, Folder 8)
      TP511
      Throssel ID #6867 "©" 07
      Throssel #758
    - Sweat Lodge Frame with Buffalo Skull (Box 3, Folder 8)
      TP512
      Negative Box 33
      Throssel ID #6X015 "©" 09
      Throssel #759
    - Sweat Lodge - Person Entering (Box 3, Folder 8)
      TP513
      Throssel #760
    - "The Remains of Camp - An Old Sweat Teepee by the River" Ookeas Illustration (Box 3, Folder 9)
      TP514
      Throssel ID #6932 "©" 08
      Throssel #761
    - "The Remains of Camp - An Old Sweat Teepee by the River" Ookeas Illustration (Box 3, Folder 9)
      TP514A
    - "Crow Lodges" (Box 3, Folder 9)
      TP515
      AHC Neg. #25701
      Throssel ID #6994 "©" 10
      Throssel #762
    - "The Homes of the Plainsmen" (Box 3, Folder 9)
      TP516
      Throssel ID #6891 "©" 07
      Throssel #763
    - "The Summer Camp" (Box 3, Folder 9)
      TP517
      Throssel ID #"©" 1991
      Throssel #764
    - Tipis - Winter (Box 3, Folder 9)
      TP518
      AHC Neg. #25731
      Throssel #765
    - Tipis - Winter (Box 3, Folder 9)
      TP519
      Throssel #766
    - "Northwinds Had Brought Much White Death" Ookeas Illustration (Box 3, Folder 10)
      TP520
      Throssel #767
    - Blackfoot Tipis (Box 3, Folder 10)
      TP521
      Throssel #768
    - Blackfoot Tipis/Wagons/Horses (Box 3, Folder 10)
      TP522
      Throssel #769
    - Blackfoot Tipis (Box 3, Folder 10)
      TP523
      Throssel #776
    - Blackfoot Tipis (Box 3, Folder 10)
      TP524
      Throssel #942
    - "A Blackfoot Lodge" (Box 3, Folder 10)
      TP525
      Throssel #953
    - "A Blackfoot Lodge" (Box 3, Folder 10)
      TP525A
      Throssel #997
    - Blackfoot Tipi (Box 3, Folder 10)
      TP526
      Throssel #993
    - Crow Tipis (Box 3, Folder 11)
      TP527
      Throssel #770
    - Tipis (Box 3, Folder 11)
      TP528
      Throssel ID #6V005 "©" 05
      Throssel #771
    - Tipis - Painted with Horses (Box 3, Folder 11)
      TP529
      Negative Box 33 and 34
      AHC Neg. #25732
      Throssel #772
    - Tipis (Box 3, Folder 11)
      TP530
      Negative Box 34
      Throssel #773
    - Tipis - Winter (Box 3, Folder 11)
      TP531
      Throssel #774
    - Tipis by River (Box 3, Folder 11)
      TP532
      Throssel #775
    - Tipi (Box 3, Folder 11)
      TP533
      Throssel #777
    - Tipis (Box 3, Folder 11)
      TP534
      Throssel #778
    - Tipis - Winter (Box 3, Folder 11)
      TP535
      Throssel #779
    - Tipis - Canvas (Box 3, Folder 11)
      TP536
      Throssel #780
    - Tipis and Arbor (Box 3, Folder 12)
      TP537
      Throssel #781
    - Tipis - Winter (Box 3, Folder 12)
      TP538
      Throssel ID #6955
      Throssel #782
    - Tipi - Ceremonial (Box 3, Folder 12)
      TP539
      Throssel #783
    - Tipis - Women - Horses (Box 3, Folder 12)
      TP540
      Throssel ID #6960
      Throssel #784
    - Tipis and Shade (Box 3, Folder 12)
      TP541
      Throssel #785
    - Tipis - Winter (Box 3, Folder 12)
      TP542
      Throssel #819
    - Tipis by River (Box 3, Folder 12)
      TP543
      Throssel #820
    - Tipis (Box 3, Folder 12)
      TP544
      Throssel #821
    - Campground (Box 3, Folder 12)
      TP545
      Throssel #822
    - Tipis by River (Box 3, Folder 12)
      TP546
      Throssel #823
    - Tipis by River (Box 3, Folder 12)
      TP547
      Throssel #824
    - Tipis and Tents by River in Winter (Box 3, Folder 13)
      TP548
      Throssel #825
    - "Camp in Winter" (Box 3, Folder 13)
      TP549
      Throssel ID #68023
      Throssel #826
    - Tipis - Winter (Box 3, Folder 13)
      TP550
      Throssel #827
    - Village (Box 3, Folder 13)
      TP551
      Throssel ID #6954
      Throssel #828
    - Campground (Box 3, Folder 13)
      TP552
      Throssel #829
    - "Evening on the Little Big Horn" (Box 3, Folder 13)
      TP553
      Throssel ID #6882 "©" 07
      Throssel #830
    - Tipis by River (Box 3, Folder 13)
      TP554
      Throssel ID #6877 "©" 07
      Throssel #831
    - Tipis by River (Box 3, Folder 13)
      TP555
      Negative Box 35
      Throssel #832
    - Tipis (Box 3, Folder 13)
      TP556
      Throssel #833
    - Tipis (Box 3, Folder 13)
      TP557
      Throssel ID #6879 "©" 07
      Throssel #834
    - Tipis/People (Box 3, Folder 14)
      TP558
      Throssel #835
    - Tipis/People (Box 3, Folder 14)
      TP559
      Throssel #836
    - "Home of the River Crow" (Box 3, Folder 14)
      TP560
      AHC Neg. #19249
      Throssel ID #6X026
      Throssel #837
      8 prints
    - "Home of the Mountain Crow" (Box 3, Folder 15)
      TP561
      Throssel ID #6860 "©" 07
      Throssel #838
    - "Nights Would Find Many Tired People in the Camps" Ookeas Illustration (Box 3, Folder 15)
      TP562
      Throssel ID #6942 "©" 08
      Throssel #839
    - "The Summer Camp - A Typical Prairie Camp" (Box 3, Folder 15)
      TP563
      Throssel ID #"©" 1917
      Throssel #840
    - Tipis by River (Box 3, Folder 16)
      TP564
      Negative Box 36
      Throssel ID #6837 "©" 07
      Throssel #841
    - "An Evening Falls" or "Sundown of the Old Life" (Box 3, Folder 16)
      TP565
      Throssel #842
    - "An Evening Falls" or "Sundown of the Old Life" (Box 3, Folder 16)
      TP565A
    - Tipis by River - Winter (Box 3, Folder 16)
      TP566
      Throssel #843
    - "In the Pryor Mountains" (Box 3, Folder 16)
      TP567
      Throssel #844
    - Tipis by River (Box 3, Folder 16)
      TP568
      Throssel #845
    - Tipis by River (Box 3, Folder 16)
      TP569
      Throssel ID # 6876 "©" 07
      Throssel #846
    - "A Secluded Home" (Box 3, Folder 17)
      TP570
      Throssel ID #6881 "©" 07
      Throssel #901
    - Tipi (Box 3, Folder 17)
      TP571
      Throssel #902
    - Tipi (Box 3, Folder 17)
      TP572
      Throssel #903
    - Tipi (Box 3, Folder 17)
      TP573
      Throssel #904
    - Tipi - Winter (Box 3, Folder 17)
      TP574
      Throssel #905
    - "Waiting" Horse by Tipi (Box 3, Folder 17)
      TP575
      Throssel #906
    - Tipis by River (Box 3, Folder 17)
      TP576
    - "The Camp on the Little Big Horn" (Box 3, Folder 17)
      TP577
      no negative (duplicate negative of print in Negative Box 36)
    - "The Camp in the Mountains" (Box 3, Folder 17)
      TP578
      Throssel ID #6V007 "©" 05
      Throssel #907
    - "The Camp in the Mountains" (Box 3, Folder 17)
      TP579
      Throssel #908
    - "A Cheyenne Home" (Box 3, Folder 18)
      TP580
      Negative Box 37
      Throssel ID #6394 "©" 07
      Throssel #909
    - Tipi - Winter (Box 3, Folder 18)
      TP581
      Throssel #910
      1 glass negative 5 x 6
    - "An Evening in the Gap - Pryor Mountains" (Box 3, Folder 18)
      TP582
      Throssel #911
    - "An Evening in the Gap - Pryor Mountains" (Box 3, Folder 18)
      TP582A
      1 glass negative 5 x 5½
    - "Their Tipi was too Stiff to Take Down so They Left it Standing Around with the White Death" (Box 3, Folder 18)
      TP583
      AHC Neg. #25150
      Throssel ID #6929 "©" 08
      Throssel #912
    - "A Cheyenne Home" (Box 3, Folder 18)
      TP584
      Throssel #913
    - Tipis by River (Box 3, Folder 19)
      TP585
      Throssel #914
    - Tipi - Wagon and Belongings (Box 3, Folder 19)
      TP586
      Throssel #915
    - Tipi (Box 3, Folder 19)
      TP587
      Throssel ID #6437 "©" 08
      Throssel #916
    - Tipi by River (Box 3, Folder 19)
      TP588
      Throssel #917
    - Tipi - Winter (Box 3, Folder 19)
      TP589
      Throssel #918
    - "A Winter Home" (Box 3, Folder 19)
      TP590
      Throssel #919
    - Tipi (Box 3, Folder 19)
      TP591
      Throssel ID #6927 "©" 08
      Throssel #920
    - Tipi (Box 3, Folder 19)
      TP592
      Throssel #921
    - Tipi (Box 3, Folder 19)
      TP593
      Throssel #922
    - Tipi (Box 3, Folder 20)
      TP594
      Throssel ID #6928 "©" 08
      Throssel #923
    - Tipi (Box 3, Folder 20)
      TP594A
    - Tipi (Box 3, Folder 20)
      TP594B
    - Tipi (Box 3, Folder 20)
      TP595
    - Tipi - Campfire (Box 3, Folder 20)
      TP596
      Throssel #924
    - Tipi (Box 3, Folder 20)
      TP597
      Throssel #925
    - Tipi and Belongings (Box 3, Folder 20)
      TP598
      Throssel #926
    - "Deserted" (Box 3, Folder 20)
      TP599
      Negative Box 38
      Throssel ID #6849 "©" 07
      Throssel #927
    - Tipi (Box 3, Folder 20)
      TP600
      Throssel #928
    - "The Camp in the Mountains" (Box 3, Folder 20)
      TP601
      Throssel #929
    - "The Camp in the Mountains" (Box 3, Folder 20)
      TP602
      Throssel ID #6990 "©" 10
      Throssel #930
    - "The Camp In The Mountains" (Box 3, Folder 20)
      TP603
      Throssel #931
    - Tipis (Box 3, Folder 21)
      TP604
    - Tipis (Box 3, Folder 21)
      TP604A
    - Tipis (Box 3, Folder 21)
      TP605
    - Tipis (Box 3, Folder 21)
      TP606
    - Tipis by River (Box 3, Folder 21)
      TP607
      Throssel #943
    - Tipis/Tents (Box 3, Folder 21)
      TP608
      Throssel #944
    - "Indians Medicine" (Box 3, Folder 21)
      TP609
      Throssel #945
    - Tipis at Night (Box 3, Folder 21)
      TP610
      Throssel ID #6919 "©" 07
      Throssel #946
    - Tipis (Box 3, Folder 21)
      TP611
      Throssel #947
    - Tipis (Box 3, Folder 21)
      TP612
      Throssel ID #6X008
      Throssel #948
    - Crow Tipis and Man (Box 3, Folder 22)
      TP613
      Throssel #949
      1 glass negative 6 x 7
    - Tipis - Winter (Box 3, Folder 22)
      TP614
      Throssel #950
    - Shades/Arbors (Box 3, Folder 22)
      TP615
      Throssel ID #6V012
      Throssel #951
    - Tipis (Box 3, Folder 22)
      TP616
      Throssel #952
    - Tipis (Box 3, Folder 22)
      TP617
      Throssel #954
    - Tipis - Belongings - Pigs (Box 3, Folder 22)
      TP618
      Throssel #955
      1 duplicate negative
    - Tipis (Box 3, Folder 22)
      TP619
      Throssel #956
    - "The Blacklodge Tipis" (Box 3, Folder 22)
      TP620
      Throssel ID #8V001 "©" 08
      Throssel #957
    - "Crow Lodges" (Box 3, Folder 23)
      TP621
      Negative Box 39
      Throssel ID #6889 "©" 07
      Throssel #990
    - Tipis (Box 3, Folder 23)
      TP622
      Throssel ID #6851 "©" 07
      Throssel #991
    - Tipis (Box 3, Folder 23)
      TP623
      Throssel #992
    - "The Three Teepees" Nov. 24, 1905 (Box 3, Folder 23)
      TP624
      Throssel ID #8V007 "©" 05
      Throssel #994
    - Tipis by River - Winter (Box 3, Folder 23)
      TP625
      Throssel #995
    - Tipis - Winter (Box 3, Folder 23)
      TP626
      Throssel #996
    - "Camp Fire No. 1" (Box 3, Folder 23)
      TP627
      Throssel ID #6916 "©" 07
      Throssel #998
    - Tipi Under Bent Tree (Box 3, Folder 23)
      TP628
    - Tree (Bent Tree) (Box 3, Folder 23)
      TP629
    - "Interior Crow Teepee" (Box 3, Folder 23)
      TP630
      Throssel ID #6811 "©" 07
    - Tipi Interior (Box 3, Folder 23)
      TP631
    - "Sunrise on Custer Battlefield" (Box 3, Folder 24)
      TP632
      Throssel ID #6X035 "©" 1911
    - "Sunrise on Custer Battlefield" (Box 3, Folder 24)
      TP632A
    - "The Three Scouts" (Box 3, Folder 24)
      TP633
      Throssel ID #694 "©" 08
    - Custer Scouts (Box 3, Folder 24)
      TP634
    - Custer Scouts (Box 3, Folder 24)
      TP635
    - Custer Scouts (Box 3, Folder 24)
      TP636
    - "Custer's Scout" (Box 3, Folder 24)
      TP637
    - Custer Monument (Box 3, Folder 24)
      TP638
    - Custer Monument/Graves (Box 3, Folder 24)
      TP639
      no negative (duplicate negative of print in Negative Box 39)
    - Custer Monument/Graves (Box 3, Folder 24)
      TP640
    - Men at Custer Monument (Box 3, Folder 24)
      TP641
    - Custer Battle - Postcard (Box 3, Folder 24)
      TP642
    - Fiftieth Anniversary of Custer Battle [?] (Box 3, Folder 24)
      TP643
      Negative Box 40
      Throssel #970
      1 celluloid negative 5½ x 3½
    - Fiftieth Anniversary (Box 3, Folder 24)
      TP644
      Throssel #971
    - Fiftieth Anniversary - with White Man Runs Him (Box 3, Folder 24)
      TP645
      Throssel #972
    - Fiftieth Anniversary (Box 3, Folder 24)
      TP646
      Throssel #973
    - Fiftieth Anniversary (Box 3, Folder 24)
      TP647
      Throssel #974
  - 4 x 5 Glass Plate Negatives and Photographs, Subseries II.
    - Architectural Detail - Unidentified (Box 4, Folder 1)
      TP648
      Throssel #975
      1 celluloid negative 3½ x 4½
    - Building - Unidentified (Box 4, Folder 1)
      TP649
      Throssel #976
    - Cheyenne Animal Dance (Box 4, Folder 1)
      TP650
    - Watching Dancers (Box 4, Folder 1)
      TP651
      Throssel #978
    - "The Departing Warriors" (Box 4, Folder 1)
      TP652
      Throssel ID #6918 "©" 08
      Throssel #979
    - Men Plowing (Box 4, Folder 1)
      TP653
      Throssel #980
    - Woman and Child (Box 4, Folder 1)
      TP654
      Throssel #984
    - "In Silent Solitude" (Box 4, Folder 1)
      TP655
      Throssel ID #6858 "©" 07
    - Burial Scaffold (Box 4, Folder 1)
      TP656
      Throssel ID #6802 "©" 06
    - Burial Scaffolds (Box 4, Folder 1)
      TP657
    - Burial Scaffolds (Box 4, Folder 1)
      TP657A
    - Burial Scaffolds (Box 4, Folder 1)
      TP658
    - Burial Scaffolds (Box 4, Folder 1)
      TP658A
    - Burial Scaffolds (Box 4, Folder 1)
      TP658B
    - "A Family Grave Scaffold" (Box 4, Folder 1)
      TP659
      Throssel ID #8V014 Nov. 24, 1905
    - Burial Scaffold (Box 4, Folder 1)
      TP660
      Throssel ID #8V009 Nov. 24, 1905
    - Burial Scaffold - Remains (Box 4, Folder 1)
      TP661
      Throssel #983
    - Children (Box 4, Folder 2)
      TP662
      Throssel #22
    - "Making a Getaway" (Box 4, Folder 2)
      TP663
      Throssel ID #406
      Throssel #23
    - Camp Scene (Box 4, Folder 2)
      TP664
      Throssel #26
    - Raising the Medicine Tipi (Box 4, Folder 2)
      TP665
      Throssel #27
    - Raising the Medicine Tipi (Box 4, Folder 2)
      TP665A
    - Camp Scene - Tipis, Wagons (Box 4, Folder 2)
      TP666
      Throssel #28
    - Camp Scene - Woman Carrying Parcel on Back (Box 4, Folder 2)
      TP667
      Throssel #28A
    - Camp Scene (Box 4, Folder 2)
      TP668
      Throssel #31
    - "Play Fellows" (Box 4, Folder 2)
      TP669
      Throssel ID #6828
      Throssel #33
    - Woman Cooking (Box 4, Folder 2)
      TP670
      Throssel #36
    - Woman Carrying Child (Box 4, Folder 2)
      TP671
      Negative Box 41
      Throssel ID #6819
      Throssel #37
    - Camp Scene (Box 4, Folder 2)
      TP672
      Throssel #39
    - Reenactment - Event (Box 4, Folder 2)
      TP673
      Throssel #40
    - Sweat Lodge Ceremony (Box 4, Folder 3)
      TP674
      Throssel #41
    - Outdoor Cooking (Box 4, Folder 3)
      TP675
      Throssel #42
    - Children (Box 4, Folder 3)
      TP676
      Throssel #43
    - Watching a Dance or Event (Box 4, Folder 3)
      TP677
      Throssel #45
    - Blackfoot Lodge (Box 4, Folder 3)
      TP678
      Throssel #47
    - Feast at the Tobacco Dance (Box 4, Folder 3)
      TP679
      Throssel #48
    - Activity - Unidentified (Box 4, Folder 3)
      TP680
      Throssel #49
    - Camp Scene - Woman (Box 4, Folder 3)
      TP681
      Throssel #50
    - Dance - Unidentified (Box 4, Folder 3)
      TP682
      Throssel #51
    - Village by River (Box 4, Folder 3)
      TP683
      Throssel #52
    - "At the? Day" (Box 4, Folder 4)
      TP684
      Throssel ID #6842
      Throssel #53
    - "From the Camp" (Box 4, Folder 4)
      TP685
      Throssel ID #4506
      Throssel #55
    - Event or Ceremony (Box 4, Folder 4)
      TP686
      Throssel #56
    - "Waiting for Rations" (Box 4, Folder 4)
      TP687
      Throssel ID #477
      Throssel #57
    - Women (Box 4, Folder 4)
      TP688
      Throssel #59
    - Blanketed Individual (Box 4, Folder 4)
      TP689
      Throssel #60
    - Women (Box 4, Folder 4)
      TP690
      Throssel #61
    - Ceremony - Non-Indian Observing (Box 4, Folder 4)
      TP691
      Throssel #62
    - Ceremony (Box 4, Folder 4)
      TP692
      Throssel #63
    - Approaching Parade, Wagon in Foreground (Box 4, Folder 4)
      TP693
      Throssel #64
    - Woman Preparing a Hide (Box 4, Folder 5)
      TP694
      Throssel #65
    - Ceremony (Box 4, Folder 5)
      TP695
      Throssel #66
    - "A Crow Camp" (Box 4, Folder 5)
      TP696
      Throssel #68
    - "Hitting the Pipe" (Box 4, Folder 5)
      TP697
      Throssel ID #465
      Throssel #69
    - "Waiting for Rations" (Box 4, Folder 5)
      TP698
      Throssel ID #6827
      Throssel #70
    - "The Wanderers" (Box 4, Folder 5)
      TP699
      Throssel ID #6813 11-1906
      Throssel #75
    - Woman at River (Box 4, Folder 5)
      TP700
      Throssel #79
    - Children at River (Box 4, Folder 5)
      TP701
      Throssel #80
    - Woman at River (Box 4, Folder 5)
      TP702
      Throssel #81
    - Woman at River (Box 4, Folder 5)
      TP703
      Throssel #82
    - Woman Washing Clothes in River (Box 4, Folder 6)
      TP704
      Throssel #83
    - Woman Washing Clothes in River (Box 4, Folder 6)
      TP705
      Throssel #84
    - "The Camp" (Box 4, Folder 6)
      TP706
      Throssel ID #6824
      Throssel #85
    - Bathers (Box 4, Folder 6)
      TP707
      Throssel #86
    - Bathers (Box 4, Folder 6)
      TP708
      Throssel #87
    - People at River (Box 4, Folder 6)
      TP709
      Throssel #88
    - People at the River (Box 4, Folder 6)
      TP710
      Throssel #89
    - Warriors Fording River (Box 4, Folder 6)
      TP711
      Throssel #90
    - Bathers - Camp in Background (Box 4, Folder 6)